Welcome back to our course project, the burger builder where we already use redux,
Geri dnm kullandmz Bergere Boulder ders projemize tekrar ho geldiniz.
we added it before but in the last module, we learned how to run asynchronous code and how to combine
Daha nce ekledik ancak son modlde asenkron kodun nasl altrlacan ve onu redoks ile nasl
that with redux
birletireceimizi rendik.
and learned a couple of other useful things too which I now also want to apply to our course project.
Ders projemize imdi de uygulamak istediim birka faydal ey rendim.
Right now, we only handle the building of the burger
imdilik sadece burgerin Boulding'i halledeceiz.
via redux,
Neden redktr
so we can add and remove ingredients and that's about it.
Dolaysyla katk maddeleri ekleyebilir ve kaldrabiliriz ve bununla ilgili.
Obviously we got a whole checkout process
Akas, btn kontrol srecimiz var.
we can enter where we of course also want to make sure that we can store this new order we create here
Tabii ki burada yarattmz yeni emri burada saklayabildiimizden emin olmak istediimiz yere girebiliriz.
once it was successfully stored on the server, also locally so that when we visit orders, we can see
Bir kere baarl bir ekilde sunucuda yerel olarak da saklandnda, sihirbaz siparilerimizde bunu
it there for example.
rnein orada grebiliyoruz.
These are all things we want to do, we want to make sure that works correctly and for that, we'll
Bunlarn doru bir ekilde altndan emin olmak istediimizde yapmak istediimiz her ey ve bunun iin baz
need some advanced redux features
gelimi Rydex zelliklerine ihtiyacmz olacak.
we learned about.
reniyoruz.
So in this module we're going to add them, we're going to add redux for handling our orders, for fetching
getirme emrini yerine getirmek iin Rydex'i ekleyeceimize inanyoruz ve son olarak
them from the server for example and we'll also optimize our reducers a little bit with all the tools
rendiiniz tm aralarla reticilerimizi biraz da optimize edeceiz. ekirdek modl.
you learned about in the last course module.
Bu modlde, rnein sunucudan bunlar
So let's get started.
yleyse balayalm.